managemyspa.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy - Zenoti | Spa and Salon Software

At Soham, Inc (Soham) we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Soham or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, Soham's "services"). 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website 

###  **INFORMATION COLLECTED**

When you sign up for Soham’s services or buy Soham’s products at www.zenoti.com (the “Site”), Soham collects and retains certain personal information. Soham receives and stores any information you enter on the Site or give to Soham in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of Soham’s services and products. Soham uses the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future services and products for you, improving Soham’s services and products, and communicating with you. 

You will find a button in the bottom left corner of many of the pages of Soham's software solution.  Clicking this button will begin the recording of all actions performed by you in the software solution.  You can choose not to use this recording feature but if used you acknowledge that all such data would be transmitted to Soham including Soham's employees who are providing support services to you.  Soham shall not be liable for any confidential information shared with its employees by you through the use of this feature.  You acknowledge that you will not have any access to any of the recordings that you create and share with Soham.

This information is collected in several ways. For example, if you sign up for Soham’s services or buy its products, the Site will collect certain personal information required to make the purchase. If you sign up for Soham’s services Soham collects all the personal information necessary to provide you with the services purchased.

If you believe that any inaccurate or inappropriate information has been obtained or disseminated through your use of the Site, please contact Soham immediately. 

### **INFORMATION SHARING**

Soham only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Soham in the following limited circumstances: 

1\. Soham has your consent. 

2\. Soham provides such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on Soham’s behalf. Soham requires that these parties agree to process such information based on Soham’s instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

3\. Soham has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable provisions of the Terms of Use Agreement, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Soham, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

4\. If Soham becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, Soham will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

5\. Soham may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non personal information, such as but not limited to the number of users who clicked on an advertisement on the Site, the number of users that clicked on any page within the Site or aggregated business performance data across a geographical region. 

Please contact Soham through our website for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data. 

###  **SECURITY OF INFORMATION**

Soham takes all appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of Soham’s data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where Soham stores personal data. 

Soham restricts access to personal information to Soham employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

###  **ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you use Soham services, Soham makes a good faith effort to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. Soham asks individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where Soham provides information access and correction, Soham performs this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

### **COOKIES**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that Soham transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable Soham’s systems to recognize your browser to provide the various features available on the Site. 

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of many of Soham’s essential features which otherwise would not be available, Soham recommends that you leave them turned on. 

###  **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Soham will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and Soham expects most such changes will be minor. Regardless, Soham will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, Soham will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact Soham any time through this web site.
